you know Finding health and dental
coverage shouldn't be an adventure
you could just call one eight seven
seven cover me it's at the bottom of the
screen
oh and uh you're not gonna find coverage
for therapeutic massages up here
told me that
what's in the treasure chest let me see
oh not the mental health coverage you
were looking for
and are you trying to find insurance for
prescription drugs in there try page 84.
oh boy you're going way too far to find
a plan that includes pre-existing
conditions like diabetes and really
you're going into space to find dental
care come on keep your feet on the
ground with Manulife cover me most plans
offer guaranteed acceptance with no
questions asked for costs not covered by
the government your search ends here
call 1-877 cover me or visit coverme.com
now